[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 106, "question": "Is this about the base?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "this", "about", "the", "base", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "DT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 107, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Mitt Romney"]}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNPS", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 122, "question": "They're going to be crucial, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "going", "to", "be", "crucial", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "JJ", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 123, "answer": "I think the first presidential debate is the biggest night of Mitt Romney's political life now because the Democrats did not stumble here.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "the", "first", "presidential", "debate", "is", "the", "biggest", "night", "of", "Mitt", "Romney", "'s", "political", "life", "now", "because", "the", "Democrats", "did", "not", "stumble", "here", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", ",", "IN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "He fact checks himself, right?", "question_tokens": ["He", "fact", "checks", "himself", ",", "right", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "PRP", ",", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "But actually, that is not even a joke.", "answer_tokens": ["But", "actually", ",", "that", "is", "not", "even", "a", "joke", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "RB", "IN", "DT", ",", "CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "VB", "DT", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP$", "NN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 156, "question": "And if you can't have him, can we have him in Britain to be prime minister?", "question_tokens": ["And", "if", "you", "ca", "n't", "have", "him", ",", "can", "we", "have", "him", "in", "Britain", "to", "be", "prime", "minister", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "PRP", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NNP", "TO", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 157, "answer": "He would very much like that, and if you would help him do that, he'd also repeal any other amendment so that you could be his vice president, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "would", "very", "much", "like", "that", ",", "and", "if", "you", "would", "help", "him", "do", "that", ",", "he", "'d", "also", "repeal", "any", "other", "amendment", "so", "that", "you", "could", "be", "his", "vice", "president", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Britain"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["UH", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 176, "question": "What did she say when you got backstage?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "say", "when", "you", "got", "backstage", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 177, "answer": "Oh, she actually came backstage and just said, Awesome.", "answer_tokens": ["Oh", ",", "she", "actually", "came", "backstage", "and", "just", "said", ",", "Awesome", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "CC", "VBD", "CC", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "RP", "."], "qSentId": 179, "question": "Was she emotional?", "question_tokens": ["Was", "she", "emotional", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 180, "answer": "She was emotional and excited and actually really fired up.", "answer_tokens": ["She", "was", "emotional", "and", "excited", "and", "actually", "really", "fired", "up", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["EX", "VBZ", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 236, "question": "From a business point of view, have you heard anything here that makes you feel infused, encouraged for the future of business under Barack Obama?", "question_tokens": ["From", "a", "business", "point", "of", "view", ",", "have", "you", "heard", "anything", "here", "that", "makes", "you", "feel", "infused", ",", "encouraged", "for", "the", "future", "of", "business", "under", "Barack", "Obama", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "NN", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "RB", "IN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 237, "answer": "There's several things, and I see it first through the eyes of someone in the energy sector.", "answer_tokens": ["There", "'s", "several", "things", ",", "and", "I", "see", "it", "first", "through", "the", "eyes", "of", "someone", "in", "the", "energy", "sector", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "JJ", "PRP", "VBP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 241, "question": "To guarantee victory, where do you still see a bit of weakness that you have to tighten up on?", "question_tokens": ["To", "guarantee", "victory", ",", "where", "do", "you", "still", "see", "a", "bit", "of", "weakness", "that", "you", "have", "to", "tighten", "up", "on", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["TO", "NN", "NN", ",", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 242, "answer": "I'm not sure I see weakness.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "not", "sure", "I", "see", "weakness", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 253, "question": "What would be good news for Barack Obama, and what would be a warning sign?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "be", "good", "news", "for", "Barack", "Obama", ",", "and", "what", "would", "be", "a", "warning", "sign", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "WP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "VBG", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 254, "answer": "I think you have to continue to see an increase in the jobs produced in the private sector.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "you", "have", "to", "continue", "to", "see", "an", "increase", "in", "the", "jobs", "produced", "in", "the", "private", "sector", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Barack Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "IN", "CD", "CD", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 262, "question": "What do you think the answer is?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "answer", "is", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 263, "answer": "Well, first of all, when Romney talked about 12 million jobs, he never laid out a plan.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "when", "Romney", "talked", "about", "12", "million", "jobs", ",", "he", "never", "laid", "out", "a", "plan", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama", "Bill Clinton"]}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "RB", "VBZ", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "POS", "IN", "NN", ",", "CC", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 314, "question": "Ari?", "question_tokens": ["Ari", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 315, "answer": "Well, I think the central issue here is that President Obama's in trouble, but Bill Clinton is not.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "the", "central", "issue", "here", "is", "that", "President", "Obama", "'s", "in", "trouble", ",", "but", "Bill", "Clinton", "is", "not", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["CD", "."], "qSentId": 319, "question": "David Gergen, your top takeaway?", "question_tokens": ["David", "Gergen", ",", "your", "top", "takeaway", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 320, "answer": "Two.", "answer_tokens": ["Two", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["David Gergen"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "VBN", "PRP", "RP", ",", "RB", "IN", "RB", "VBG", "PRP", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What's your assessment?", "question_tokens": ["What", "'s", "your", "assessment", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "You know, I think he probably just broadened it out, rather than just having it Google-specific.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "I", "think", "he", "probably", "just", "broadened", "it", "out", ",", "rather", "than", "just", "having", "it", "Google-specific", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["China"]}, "docId": "120906pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 354, "question": "And it's interesting he mentioned Steve Jobs -- he mentioned Steve Jobs, and most of the work that Apple does is where?", "question_tokens": ["And", "it", "'s", "interesting", "he", "mentioned", "Steve", "Jobs", "--", "he", "mentioned", "Steve", "Jobs", ",", "and", "most", "of", "the", "work", "that", "Apple", "does", "is", "where", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "CC", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBZ", "WRB", "."], "aSentId": 355, "answer": "In China.", "answer_tokens": ["In", "China", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Apple"], "PERSON": ["Steve Jobs"]}}]